Guide to the Planned Community Archives collection, 1960-2009
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 8: Newspapers 1965-1999, 2004
  - Subseries 2: The Reston Times, 1968-1999, 2004
    - The Reston Times - Sprucing Up For Christmas, December 11, 1969 (Box 359, Folder 36)
    - The Reston Times - Wellborn Named to School Board, December 18, 1969 (Box 359, Folder 37)
    - The Reston Times - A Wintry Day in Reston, December 25, 1969 (Box 359, Folder 38)
    - The Reston Times - Winter Comes to Reston, January 1, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 1)
    - The Reston Times - Don't Do Something: Stand There, January 8, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 2)
    - The Reston Times - The Great Falls of the Potomac, January 15, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - The Reston Times - When Will It Ever End?, January 22, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - The Reston Times - Party lines were crossed..., January 29, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 5)
    - The Reston Times - RCA Elects President At Large, February 5, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 6)
    - The Reston Times - Pool Plan in SHOA Meeting/"A Boy Scout is Clean...", February 12, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 7)
    - The Reston Times - Georgetown Okays Health Care, February 19, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 8)
    - The Reston Times - Health Dept. Plans Rubella Clinic Here, February 26, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 9)
    - The Reston Times - SHOA Confronted by Hard Choices, March 5, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 10)
    - The Reston Times - Dr. William Feller Named Planner for Reston-Georgetown Health Care, March 12, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 11)
    - The Reston Times - NoVa Music Center Opens 1970 Drive, March 19, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 12)
    - The Reston Times - Plaza Fountain/Rubella Clinic Slated at Intermediate School, March 26, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 13)
    - The Reston Times - Brush Fire, April 2, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 14)
    - The Reston Times - SHOA Dissidents Respond to Criticisms of Actions, April 9, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 15)
    - The Reston Times - Earth Day: People, Cities and the Land, April 16, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 16)
    - The Reston Times - Maps for Environmental Grand Tour, April 23, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 17)
    - The Reston Times - WMATC Praises Commuter Bus, April 30, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 18)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA Board Adopts Plan for Structure, May 7, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 19)
    - The Reston Times - Fish Story!/LANK Fair Set for Saturday, May 14, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 20)
    - The Reston Times - Top HUD Official Will Be Keynoter Saturday Morning, May 21, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 21)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA Elections/New Bus Proposed, May 28, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 22)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA Village Council Candidates, June 4, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 23)
    - The Reston Times - Dulles Airport Unwilling Host to Hijacker, June 11, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 24)
    - The Reston Times - Kitten in the Shop, June 18, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 25)
    - The Reston Times - Lake Time, June 25, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 25)
    - The Reston Times - "I Think That I Shall Never See...", July 2, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 27)
    - The Reston Times - Fireworks on the Fourth, July 9, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 28)
    - The Reston Times - Dulles Transit study Announced by Spong, July 16, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 29)
    - The Reston Times - Riding at Reston South Stables, July 23, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 30)
    - The Reston Times - Newpaper Collections Will Aid Pollution Fight, July 30, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 31)
    - The Reston Times - Reston May Get "Breakthrough" Project, August 6, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 32)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA Sets Agenda for Town Council, August 13, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 33)
    - The Reston Times - U.S.G.S. Move Gets Closer, August 20, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 34)
    - The Reston Times - Reston Designated as Site of New Communities Center, August 27, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 35)
    - The Reston Times - Black Arts Festival Opens/RCC Gets Priest, September 3, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 36)
    - The Reston Times - no title, September 10, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 37)
    - The Reston Times - Play at the Day Care Center, September 17, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 38)
    - The Reston Times - NEA Purchases 30 Acre Tract, September 24, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 39)
    - The Reston Times - Six Month Residents May Register Here, October 1, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 40)
    - The Reston Times - RCA Plaza Pancakes, October 8, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 41)
    - The Reston Times - Reston Times Backs Hoofnagle, Stearns, October 15, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 42)
    - The Reston Times - RCA Conclave to Examine Hunters Woods Rezoning, October 22, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 43)
    - The Reston Times - Good Work...If you can get it!, October 29, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 44)
    - The Reston Times - "Mousetrap" Opens Friday, November 5, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 45)
    - The Reston Times - Common Ground Reduces Hours, November 12, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 46)
    - The Reston Times - Teens to Assist on Patrol, November 19, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 47)
    - The Reston Times - no title, November 26, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 48)
    - The Reston Times - Leaf Burning Issue Warms Up, December 3, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 49)
    - The Reston Times - no title, December 10, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 50)
    - The Reston Times - Changes in Common Ground/Tree Lighting Set, December 17, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 51)
    - The Reston Times - Santa Makes Grand Entrance, December 24, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 52)
    - The Reston Times - Reston Sunset, December 31, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 53)
    - The Reston Times - First Snow of the New Year, January 7, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - The Reston Times - no title, January 14, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - The Reston Times - no title, January 21, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - The Reston Times - "Run for Your Life", January 28, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - The Reston Times - RCA's "Justification" (An Editorial), February 4, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 5)
    - The Reston Times - Ramps Open/RCA Presidential Hopefuls, February 11, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 6)
    - The Reston Times - RCA Elects Board, President Saturday, February 18, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 7)
    - The Reston Times - Players Open Bell, Book and Candle Friday, February 25, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 8)
    - The Reston Times - Wilton Park: An Institution Worth Imitation, March 4, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 9)
    - The Reston Times - '72 County Budget Seeks Tax Increase..., March 11, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 10)
    - The Reston Times - no title, March 18, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 11)
    - The Reston Times - Feeling Free at the Reston Free School, March 25, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 12)
    - The Reston Times - Forest Edge Elementary Grows Like Topsy, April 1, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 13)
    - The Reston Times - Red Cross Blood Unit Will Visit, April 8, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 14)
    - The Reston Times - Reston's Eco-Symbol: Story on Walkway, April 15, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 15)
    - The Reston Times - Spring! Restonians Find that Warm Weather..., April 22, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 16)
    - The Reston Times - Doing Your Own Thing..., April 29, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 17)
    - The Reston Times - Elder Tournament at Reston Club, May 6, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 18)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA Petitions Due By Tomorrow Evening, May 13, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 19)
    - The Reston Times - Move toward tax district starts/Special Issue, May 20, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 20)
    - The Reston Times - Judge Bryant denies injunction, May 27, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 21)
    - The Reston Times - Victims of Dogbite/Tax District Meeting, June 3, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 22)
    - The Reston Times - kaleidoscope: a creative experience for children, June 10, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 23)
    - The Reston Times - Where It's At! There Will Be a Rock Concert..., June 17, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 24)
    - The Reston Times - Cuing Up!/Where It's At!, June 24, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 25)
    - The Reston Times - USGS Construction Contract Signed, July 1, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 26)
    - The Reston Times - MITRE Unveils Two-Way CATV, July 8, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 27)
    - The Reston Times - no title, July 15, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 28)
    - The Reston Times - Gulf Reston Reveals Future Development, July 22, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 29)
    - The Reston Times - Official USGS Groundbreaking Ceremonies Saturday, July 29, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 30)
    - The Reston Times - USGS Groundbreaking/Reston Drug Bust Nabs 4, August 5, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - The Reston Times - Police Bust Drug "Farm", August 12, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - The Reston Times - no title, August 19, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - The Reston Times - Wall Collapses at Cedar Ridge: 2 Girls Injured, August 26, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - The Reston Times - Filene Concert Festival Highlight, Septemeber 2, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 5)
    - The Reston Times - Scenes from the Black Arts Festival, September 9, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 6)
    - The Reston Times - Forest Edge School Opens, September 16, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 7)
    - The Reston Times - 9 Year Old Sucked into Sewer, September 23, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 8)
    - The Reston Times - The Reston Commuter Bus, September 30, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 9)
    - The Reston Times - Fire Truck Visits Plaza Saturday, October 7, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 10)
    - The Reston Times - "Wait Until Dark", October 14, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 11)
    - The Reston Times - Making Posters for the FEES Bookfair, October 21, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 12)
    - The Reston Times - Vote Tuesday/Planning Reston Schools, October 28, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 13)
    - The Reston Times - Swingers...and voters, November 4, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 14)
    - The Reston Times - Study Team Findings Come Out Monday/Fire in Northgate, November 11, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 15)
    - The Reston Times - Fire in Herndon, November 18, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 16)
    - The Reston Times - Colvin Mill: Craftsmanship in Wood, November 25, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 17)
    - The Reston Times - Learning by Doing at Lake Anne School..., December 2, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 18)
    - The Reston Times - The hunter Woods Village Center, December 9, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 19)
    - The Reston Times - Route 7 Wreck Fatal to Hunters Woods Woman, December 16, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 20)
    - The Reston Times - Schools to Request $143.6 million, December 23, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 21)
    - The Reston Times - The Year in Review: the first six months, December 30, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 22)
    - The Reston Times - Moon over the High Rise, January 6, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 1)
    - The Reston Times - Safeway shopping carts get the strangest passengers!!, January 13, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 2)
    - The Reston Times - Which Kids Ride Buses Next Year?, January 20, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - The Reston Times - Study Team Bares Work, January 27, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 4)
    - The Reston Times - Schools advised to Pursue Normal Bond Policy (incomplete), February 3, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 5)
    - The Reston Times - Players' "Journey" Begins Friday, February 10, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 6)
    - The Reston Times - The 1972 Candidates for the RCA Board, February 17, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 7)
    - The Reston Times - Freeman Chosen First Student Member of School Board, February 24, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 8)
    - The Reston Times - Fire Follows School Bus Wreck in HW, March 2, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 9)
    - The Reston Times - "Slave" Auction Stirs Reactions, March 9, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 10)
    - The Reston Times - GRI flexes RHOA muscle, March 16, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 11)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA Board Poll Set May 6, March 23, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 12)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA Election Rules/Candidate Profiles, March 30, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 13)
    - The Reston Times - Concern: RCA Focuses Community's Attention on Schools, April 6, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 14)
    - The Reston Times - no title, April 13, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 15)
    - The Reston Times - Dogwood Elementary School Plans Approved, April 20, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 16)
    - The Reston Times - Blookmobile Visits/Dog Problems/Elderly Tax Relief, April 27, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 17)
    - The Reston Times - RCA Pushes Voter Registration for June 13 School Referendum, May 4, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 18)
    - The Reston Times - You Must Register by Saturday to Vote June 13, May 11, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 19)
    - The Reston Times - No Tax Increase This Year, May 18, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 20)
    - The Reston Times - Reston Lines Co. Coffers, VPI Says, May 25, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 21)
    - The Reston Times - Bulldozer rips Uplands gas line, June 1, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 22)
    - The Reston Times - Autopsy Shows Murder Caused Gwen (Ames)'s Death, June 8, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 23)
    - The Reston Times - School Bond Fails/Suzette Opens Friday, June 15, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 24)
    - The Reston Times - no title, June 22, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 25)
    - The Reston Times - Shock Victim Dies/Finally: Agreement on RHAC!, June 29, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 26)
    - The Reston Times - Fourth Marred By Lake Anne Drowning, July 6, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 1)
    - The Reston Times - County Vetoes Sewer Applications, July 13, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 2)
    - The Reston Times - Referendum Deferral Threatens Tough Times Ahead in Reston, July 20, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 3)
    - The Reston Times - Board Refuses $1.8 Million School Loan, July 27, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - The Reston Times - Supervisors (Almost) Approve Nov. Referendum, August 3, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 5)
    - The Reston Times - 5 Yr. Plan Foresees Growth or Deficits, August 10, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 6)
    - The Reston Times - 22090 or 22091: Reston Will Get Its Own ZIP Codes, August 17, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 7)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA Closes Investigation...OSHA Doesn't, August 24, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 8)
    - The Reston Times - Fletcher Kicks Off Arts Festival, August 31, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 9)
    - The Reston Times - Festival: Bonds Not Forgotten, September 7, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 10)
    - The Reston Times - Herndon Faces Growing Crisis, September 7, 1972 (should be Sept. 14) (Box 364, Folder 11)
    - The Reston Times - Transportation Picture Improving: Ramps Delayed/Metro Extended, September 21, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 12)
    - The Reston Times - Police St(ation) Planned; Road Needed, September 28, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 13)
    - The Reston Times - Highrise Decision Deferred, October 5, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 14)
    - The Reston Times - John Wells Headed For Hanoi, October 12, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 15)
    - The Reston Times - Kelley Will Leave County Post, October 19, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 16)
    - The Reston Times - Study Shows Reston "Profit", October 26, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 17)
    - The Reston Times - Wells Terms Bombing "Failure", November 2, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 18)
    - The Reston Times - Packard, GOP Records Wins/Board Acts on Dulles Noise, November 9, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 19)
    - The Reston Times - School Decision May Be Deferred, November 16, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 20)
    - The Reston Times - Schools Target in on 45-15 Plan, November 23, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 21)
    - The Reston Times - 5 Year Plan Would Harm Reston, November 30, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 22)
    - The Reston Times - Old-New School Rift Persists, December 7, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 23)
    - The Reston Times - Bond Package Revealed/RHOA Budget Talks Continue, December 14, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 24)
    - The Reston Times - '74 School Budget Banks On Drop In Enrollment, December 21, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 25)
    - The Reston Times - Wasserman Times Man of the Year, December 28, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 26)
    - The Reston Times - GRI-Hospital Sign Contract, January 4, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - The Reston Times - Wiehle and North Shore Get Light, January 11, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - The Reston Times - Interfaith Breaking Ground, January 18, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - The Reston Times - Decision Deferred on 624 Acre Rezoning, January 25, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - The Reston Times - Board Defers Rezoning Decision, February 1, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 5)
    - The Reston Times - County Protests Loss of School Aid, February 8, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 6)
    - The Reston Times - Impact Aid Clouds School Budget, February 15, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 7)
    - The Reston Times - Emergency Care Unit Proposed, February 22, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 8)
    - The Reston Times - Voters Elect Page RCA Chief, March 1, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 9)
    - The Reston Times - Sen. Scott Pushes I-66 Completion, March 8, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 10)
    - The Reston Times - "Uncertainty" Major Theme of '74 County Budget, March 15, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 11)
    - The Reston Times - Dulles Should Be "USA Gateway Port", March 22, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 12)
    - The Reston Times - First Hospital Hurdle April 12, March 29, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 13)
    - The Reston Times - Board to Consider Land Use Program, April 5, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 14)
    - The Reston Times - County Grapples With Growth, April 12, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 15)
    - The Reston Times - Reston to Show $16.7 Million Tax Surplus by 1982, April 19, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 16)
    - The Reston Times - Hospital "Choice" Is "Back-up", April 26, 1973 (Box 365, Folder 17)
    - The Reston Times - Board Vetoes Peterson Rezoning, May 3, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - The Reston Times - County Pushes Dulles Metro Line, May 10, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - The Reston Times - Board Adopts Land Use Plans, May 17, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - The Reston Times - Transportation: Looks Grim!, May 24, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 4)
    - The Reston Times - Transportation: Reston The Island, May 31, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 5)
    - The Reston Times - Shipp's Record Stays Closed, June 7, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 6)
    - The Reston Times - Bond Referendum Approved!/USGS Hassle Near Resolution, June 14, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 7)
    - The Reston Times - GUCHP Prepaid (Health) Plan Available, June 21, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 8)
    - The Reston Times - (PDH) Development Proposed, June 28, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 9)
    - The Reston Times - Confusion Mars Tall Oaks Voting, July 5, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 10)
    - The Reston Times - WMATA Threatens (Reston Commuter Bus) Hike, July 12, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 11)
    - The Reston Times - Schools OK Vending Project/Free Bus Needs Help, July 19, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 12)
    - The Reston Times - Board Adopts Land Use Policy, July 26, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 13)
    - The Reston Times - Gov(ernment) Study Urges "Councils", August 2, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 14)
    - The Reston Times - County Agrees with Booz-Allen, August 9, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 15)
    - The Reston Times - Area School Population Soars, August 16, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 16)
    - The Reston Times - Tenants Protest 8% Rent Hike, August 23, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 17)
    - The Reston Times - RCA Urges Rezoning Support, August 30, 1973 (Box 366, Folder 18)
    - The Reston Times - County Studies Year Round Again, September 6, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 1)
    - The Reston Times - Board Ok's Rezonings.../Commuter Bus Faces Rate Hike, September 13, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 2)
    - The Reston Times - Hospital Approval Hits Snag, September 20, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - The Reston Times - 4 Highrise Condos Proposed For (Hunters Woods), September 27, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 4)
    - The Reston Times - Letters Air Hospital Options, October 4, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 5)
    - The Reston Times - Protestors Object to Info Move, October 11, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 6)
    - The Reston Times - School Board Vetoes HIS Renovation, Will Rebuild..., October 18, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 7)
    - The Reston Times - Fellowship Addition Snagged/Candidates' Night Set Nov. 2, October 25, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 8)
    - The Reston Times - 50% Voter Turnout Predicted, November 1, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 9)
    - The Reston Times - Reston backs Howell, Cahill, November 8, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 10)
    - The Reston Times - Accused Rapist Arrested/50mph Limit Asked on Rt. 7, November 15, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 11)
    - The Reston Times - Schools, County Face Fuel Crisis/Let It Snow!, November 22, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 12)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA May Face Dues Hike, November 29, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 13)
    - The Reston Times - Beverly to Seek RPC Rezoning For Hospital Site, December 6, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 14)
    - The Reston Times - 20 Band to Sue Ryland/"Capture" Caps Coppers' Caper, December 13, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 14)
    - The Reston Times - Schools Seek 12.2% Increase, December 20, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 15)
    - The Reston Times - RHOA Okays $10 Dues Hike, December 27, 1973 (Box 367, Folder 16)
    - The Reston Times, January 3, 1974 - June 27, 1974 (Box 368)
    - The Reston Times, July 4, 1974 - December 26, 1974 (Box 369)
    - The Reston Times, January 2, 1975 - May 1, 1975 (Box 370)
    - The Reston Times, May 8, 1975 - August 28, 1975 (Box 371)
    - The Reston Times, September 11, 1975 - December 25, 1975 (Box 372)
    - The Reston Times, January 1, 1976 - August 12, 1976 (4/29, 5/6, 5/13, 5/20/76 missing) (Box 373)
    - The Reston Times, April 13, 1978 - June 22, 1978 (Box 374)
    - The Reston Times, July 6, 1978 - September 28, 1978 (Box 375)
    - The Reston Times, October 5, 1978 - December 28, 1978 (Box 376)
    - The Reston Times, January 4, 1979 - March 29, 1979 (Box 377)
    - The Reston Times, April 5, 1979 - June 28, 1979 (Box 378)
    - The Reston Times, July 5, 1979 - September 27, 1979 (Box 379)
    - The Reston Times, October 4, 1979 - December 27, 1979 (Box 380)
    - The Reston Times, January 3. 1980 - April 24, 1980 (2/14/80 missing) (Box 381)
    - The Reston Times, May 1, 1980 - June 26, 1980 (Box 382)
    - The Reston Times, July 3, 1980 - September 25, 1980 (Box 383)
    - The Reston Times, October 2, 1980 - December 25, 1980 (Box 384)
    - The Reston Times, January 1, 1981 - March 26, 1981 (Box 385)
    - The Reston Times, April 2, 1981 - June 25, 1981 (Box 386)
    - The Reston Times, July 2, 1981 - September 24, 1981 (Box 387)
    - The Reston Times, October 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 388)
    - The Reston Times, January 7, 1982 - March 25, 1982 (Box 389)
    - The Reston Times, April 1, 1982 - June 24, 1982 (Box 390)
    - The Reston Times, July 1, 1982 - September 30, 1982 (7/22/82 missing) (Box 391)
    - The Reston Times, October 7, 1982 - December 30, 1982 (Box 392)
    - The Reston Times, January 6, 1983 - March 31, 1983 (2/24/83 missing) (Box 393)
    - The Reston Times, April 7, 1983 - June 30, 1983 (Box 394)
    - The Reston Times, July 7, 1983 - September 29, 1983 (Box 395)
    - The Reston Times, October 6, 1983 - December 29, 1983 (Box 396)
    - The Reston Times, January 5, 1984 - March 29, 1984 (2/23, 3/1, 3/15/84 missing) (Box 397)
    - The Reston Times, April 5, 1984 - June 28, 1984 (6/7/84 missing) (Box 398)
    - The Reston Times, July 5, 1984 - September 27, 1984 (Box 399)
    - The Reston Times, October 4, 1984 - December 27, 1984 (Box 400)
    - The Reston Times, January 3, 1985 - April 11, 1985 (3/21/85 missing) (Box 401)
    - The Reston Times, April 18, 1985 - June 27, 1985 (Box 402)
    - The Reston Times, July 4, 1985 - September 26, 1985 (Box 403)
    - The Reston Times, October 2, 1985 - November 13, 1985 (starts twice a week publication) (Box 404)
    - The Reston Times, November 16, 1985 - December 25, 1985 (Box 405)
    - The Reston Times, January 1, 1986 - February 26, 1986 (Box 406)
    - The Reston Times, March 1, 1986 - April 30, 1986 (Box 407)
    - The Reston Times, May 3, 1986 - June 28, 1986 (back to weekly publication after 6/28) (Box 408)
    - The Reston Times, July 2, 1986 - September 24, 1986 (8/6/86 missing) (Box 409)
    - The Reston Times, October 1, 1986 - December 31, 1986 (Box 410)
    - The Reston Times, January 7, 1987 - March 25, 1987 (Box 414)